equitynet.com 2019-07-22

# EquityNet Privacy Policy

| 

At EquityNet, we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to the online products and services offered by Global Equity Fintech, Inc or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, EquityNet "services"). 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us

**Information we collect and how we use it**

We offer a service that requires you to register for an account and provide some personal and business information to us. In order to provide our services, we may collect the following types of information: 

| •  |  **Personal information** – When you sign up for an EquityNet account, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, address, phone number, email address, and account username and password). We also request that our customers provide credit card or other payment account information, which is encrypted and securely maintained at Authorize.Net. This information is collected for internal use only and will not be sold to or shared with third-party firms.   
---|---  
•  |  **Business information** – We may collect business information that may be used by us in an anonymous aggregate form. This information will not be used with an identification of individual users or individual businesses. Transparency of user and business data related to an identifiable business is restricted to recipient users who have been specifically authorized to view such information by the originating and authorizing user.   
•  |  **Information security** – We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These security measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to personal information by EquityNet employees and third party service providers who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.   
•  |  **User communications** – Email or other communication sent to EquityNet, may be retained in order to process your inquiries, to respond to your requests, and to improve our services.   
•  |  **Affiliated sites** – We may offer links to other websites as part of our services. Personal information that you provide directly to such sites may constitute privacy issues outside the bounds of the EquityNet Privacy Policies. EquityNet does not exercise control over linked sites and does not collect information as a result of your contact with those sites.   
•  |  **Business merger or acquisition** – In the event that Global Equity Fintech, Inc goes through a business merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, personal and business information may be among the assets transferred. Global Equity Fintech, Inc will provide notification on its website for a minimum of 30 days if any such change in ownership takes place.   
•  |  **Loss of information** – By using the site, you agree to hold-harmless and indemnify EquityNet from accidental loss or dissemination of information.   
  
**Cookies and Related Technologies**

The EquityNet website uses cookies and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. 

**Enforcement**

EquityNet will regularly review its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or EquityNet's use of information by contacting us via our website. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is EquityNet’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of data that cannot be resolved between EquityNet and an individual. 

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes to our Privacy page, and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes).
